Greg Munro

Web Developer

Young professional living in Barcelona since 2016. In 2020 decided to change career paths due to the pandemic and follow interests in Web Development. In December 2021, proudly graduated from Ironhack Barcelona, after an intensive 3 month web development bootcamp.

During this time, learnt to create one page applications using React, API, Node.js, Express, Mongoose, MongoDB CSS3, HTML5, Tailwind, Bootstrap and Javascript. Before this, professional background was in music-licensing, publishing and talent management. With a previously demonstrated history in live-performance as a session-guitarist.

Contact

Mobile:

+34 622568805

Email:

gregmunro90@gmail.com

Website:

www.greg-munro.com

Address:

c/ Bruc 65, 08009 Barcelona

Experience

Web Development experience

- Sport Buddy https://sport--buddy.herokuapp.com/ A full stack mobile first application, used to find sporting events in Barcelona. Tech stack: React, MongoDB, Express, Node, Tailwind
- Berghain Bootcamp https://gmunro90.github.io/Berghain-Bootcamp/
 A browser based quiz game, users attempt to enter Berlin's infamous nightclub Tech stack: HTML5, CSS3, Javscript (ES6)

International Copyright Coordinator Concord Music Publishing, London | Jan 2021 - Oct 2021

- Implement copyright d across Pop, Jazz and Media catalogs, administrating copyright data of over 260,000 works, bulk registering copyright data via CWR, ingesting sub-publisher data.
- Maintained royalty databases, database population, new works and agreements registration across 5 continents.
- Liaised with PRS/MCPS, ICE and international societies on all matters relating to works and catalogs
- Resolution of duplicate claims and conflicts at performance and mechanical rights organisations.

Booking Agent Analog. Barcelona | Jan 2019 - Mar 2020

- Tour schedule management of 6 high profile, international electronic musical artists
- Negotiated performance contracts with promoters, venues and festivals worldwide
- Facilitate logistical assistants with touring administration, visa processing and legal assets

Logistics & Tour Administration Assistant B4 Bookings. Barcelona | Nov 2016 - Nov 2018

- Global logistics manager for 45 touring electronic music artists
- Issued contracts, invoices, itineraries, performance visas
- Booked travel, diary, and crew management for worldwide tours for 500+ events per year
- Uploaded and maintained records of contractual, logistical, accounting info onto a bespoke system, overseeing team of 8 assistants

Education & Qualifications

Ironhack, Barcelona | Sept - Dec 2021

Full Stack Web Development | React, Javascript (ES6), MongoDB, Express, Node, HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, Bootstrap

Berklee College of Music, Remote | March - Sept 2020 Diploma | Music Supervision

University of West London, London | Sept 2009 - June 2012 BMus (Hons) | Music Performance

London College of Music | Sept 2008 - June 2009 Higher Diploma | Music Practice

Languages

English - Native Spanish - Advanced